<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Funny</title>
    <link>https://www.geekgame.site/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Funny</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2008–2018, Steve Francia and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.geekgame.site/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.geekgame.site/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.geekgame.site/en/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my blog! As a programmer, I am enthusiastic about documenting and sharing the challenges I encounter and the knowledge I acquire in my work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The main purpose of this blog is to record my technical growth journey, and I hope these contents can help fellow technology enthusiasts like me. Here are the main areas I focus on:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cloud Native: From architecture design to practical applications, I am dedicated to exploring how cloud native technologies can enhance the scalability, reliability, and resilience of systems.&#xA;Edge Computing: Investigating the applications and technical implementations of edge computing, and how performing computation and storage near data sources can reduce latency and increase efficiency.&#xA;Containers: Researching the latest developments in container technology, including tips and best practices for using Docker and Kubernetes to achieve more efficient application deployment and management.&#xA;Here, you will find detailed technical articles, practical experiences, case studies, and my insights on the latest technology trends. I believe that as long as we keep learning and sharing, we can all find our own path in the ocean of technology.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
